Inventory of the Flora Adams Darling Papers 1862-1908
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Addition to Collection, 1993.59, 1883-1902, n.d. (Box 1-2)
  - Genealogical material. (Box-folder 1:1-13)
    Material on the Darling and related families including Robb family, Adams family, Rowell family, Duston family, Klingle family, and Tiernan family. Also included are Robb-Darling court records, wills, and documents.
  - The Darlings - recollections of Miss Helen Robb to James S. Patton. (Box-folder 1:14)
  - Photo album with index identifying photos., MsV.1. (Box 2)
  - Photo album with few photos identified., MsV.2. (Box 2)
  - Scrapbook of clippings and letters compiled by Mrs. Darling about her son's death., MsV.3. (Box 2)
  - Mrs. Darling's Letters, or Memories of the Civil War by Mrs. Flora Adams Darling. New York; John W. Lovell Company, 1883., V.4. (Box 2)
  - Three documents from the October Term 1902 of the Court of Appeals of the District of Columbia, 1902., Vol. 5-7. (Box 2)
    The Washington Loan and Trust Company, Nancy Darling and Charles Tiernan Darling, Appellants, vs. Flora Adams Darling. Includes Brief for appellants, Appellee's brief, and Appeal from the Supreme Court of the District of Columbia.